oh let's go I don't ever put a take
profit number because you could just
literally have your take profits run as
far as you want you want to cut your
stock you want to cut your oh
Olive is like yo what the
well I was explaining on the live stream
this is why I don't place a take profit
that's the whole point of the setup
forget oh my
all right so this giveaway is for the
people that participated in the rocket
challenge the only way for you to know
what that is you have to join the free
telegram the winner that lands in the
top 10 in the leaderboard is going to
win
or PS5 why did I put the PS5 in the
bathroom I don't know I was late at
night I was on the phone and I just
threw it in there but I have another
giveaway for all of you guys that
subscribe to the channel as soon as I
hit 75k YouTube literally tells me who
subscribes to the channel when I hit 75k
I have another PS5 coming to every
single person that not every single
person that subscribes as possible as
soon as we hit 75k Subs I have an even
bigger giveaway coming for you guys so
stay tuned to the next video let's get
in with the video
[Music]
well first of all shout out to Sensei
for Lending me the years for two weeks
because he went on a trip now and I'm
like yo I'm thinking of getting the
years that many years because it's
either I'm in between the years or a
cullinan everybody out here in Miami has
a years in my opinion I think it's
played out like you go to a red light
you can mix of yours for an Audi it's
just my opinion I could be completely
wrong but you can't mix a color name
with anything it's a huge box so first
of all shout out to signs that for
Lending me the the years for two weeks
but in this video we're going to be
talking about key points that got me to
make those 60k how I managed it the risk
management the approach pretty much
everything that got me in order to get
that trade and then the most important
for me myself I honestly think is the
psychology the mindset behind it the you
know risk tolerance how I actually did
about it and that is the last one in the
video so make sure to watch the video
all the way to the end because I want to
give you guys pretty much my whole
entire route on how I did it all right
so first things first is you need a
ginger shot to start off the day so
you're active your brain is active
everything is ready if you guys haven't
had a ginger shop I highly encourage it
they're amazing
[Music]
all right so rule number one is top
analysis so every single Sunday I get on
a webinar with the guys in the guy that
boot camp in the Discord and I host a
class where I go through every single
pair that I trade so I have a full watch
list of bears I probably trade maybe 15
16 pairs that I actually watch but it
doesn't mean that I actually trade them
so I'll do a full top down analysis and
I'll pick the top three top four
whatever trades I have the best
probabilities and going in that
direction I usually take trades that
have all three time frames in sync so
I'm a pro Trend Trader meaning I've only
tried to take a trade if the weekly
timeframe is bullish daily time for Miss
bullish in the four hour time from his
footage at that point I'm going with the
trend right so if you want the more the
majority of the probably needs to be in
your favorite that's exactly what I did
with gold golden ended up in the top
three of that watch this and I ended up
trading with the weekly daily and in the
four hour we're all bullish which got me
to make that trade to hit 60k so that's
my rule number one doing a full proper
top analysis taking the top three pairs
top four pairs for the week that I'm
going to be trading for that one
so the next very crucial point is
setting areas of inches and where I'm
looking to take the trade right so let's
say we're bullish we're creating higher
highs I want the market to create a
higher low in the case of gold we're
waiting for gold to give us a pullback
to our area of Interest once it gets to
this area of Interest I was looking to
buy so the main important thing is you
need to after understanding what the
trend is doing whether we're going to
offer a downside setting your top Pairs
and you need to set the air of Interest
or where you're looking to buy at the
Zone all right so we're here at the bank
right now bought a deposit my 50 million
that I made on Dodge Coin
no I'm kidding all right guys so the
next point which is point number three
or four whatever point we're on which is
the most important one which is setting
your alarms right so every point is
important but how do you know when
you're gonna get into a trade if you
haven't set your alarm so after we
already set our area of interest you set
your alarm at that area of interest and
you want it to be hit obviously when
you're in session whether it's New York
a London session but when your alarms
get hit you want to make sure you're
active in front of the computer your
phone whatever the case is and then
you're taking the trade in the session
that you're meant to take it I
personally only take trades London maybe
pre-london New York maybe a little bit
pre New York and that's it anything
after that it's pretty much no movement
in the markets and let's get into the
next one let me get uh let me get one
birthday cake pop make it to one
birthday cake two two birthday cake pops
the pink ones all right two birthday
cake pops that's it yeah we don't need
more of them the next key component is
setting your confluences in order to
take the trade right so it is super
important to make sure you have all your
influences lined up right us a swing
training lab within the guy to boot camp
we have a series of conferences we need
to meet in order to take the trade
pretty simple ones are the first one
that I already said you need to have
three time frames Instinct so you're
approach on trading you're obviously
trading with the trend that's number one
number two you gotta be buying at a
solid area of Interest how do I find an
area of interest just watch the other
videos or I can make a video on it just
drop a comment below if you want me to
do that
um third is you want to make sure you
have the proper session when you're
taking the trade whether it's New York
or London after you need your entry
signal you want to make sure you have
the proper entry signal when entering
the trade after the entry signal you got
to make sure your stop loss and take
profit are you know worth it because if
you're having a trade that's a
one-to-one risk to reward it's just not
worth it you got to have a minimum but
one to two point five minimum or one to
two point five because 2.5 percent is
2.5 a week is 10 a month so that's super
key once you have all these confluences
added up you pretty much you know you
grade your trade we have a specific way
how we grade our trades but you can
grade it anywhere from an a setup BC or
D I personally myself I don't like
taking setups that are under a v setup
because it's just not worth the money
and then after that you pretty much just
set them forget so
[Music]
the hardest part
so this trade was actually in my free
telegram if you haven't joined my fee
telegram I highly encourage you to go
through so not only do I give trades all
the time but I you know also do
giveaways in their randomly like how I
just did with this last one with rocket
but leading us to our last and I believe
is the most important
um tip trick whatever you want to call
it when it comes to trading that is
mindset the psychology of trading so
there's three three very key important
uh three very key important components
when it comes to trading that's going to
be your stop-loss placement how to
properly set and forget and don't set
and forget too much because then you
mess everything up when it comes to
taking your trade and putting a stop
loss you need to be 100 okay with that
trade hitting your stop loss immediately
because if it hits it immediately and
then you want to get back into it or get
that money back at that point you're not
okay with what you're risking so lower
your risk whatever I rinsed on this
trade to make 60k I simply was a hundred
percent when it came with it and if I
would have hit my stop loss I would have
moved on to the next trade my point two
would be set it forget the proper way
don't be attached to the money you hear
me say it in the recording I'm trying to
make a logical trading decision right
now I don't want to close this trade
because of the money right that's not
the point the point is to close the
position if it's the right time to close
so as of right now that's kind of what
I'm debating we are pulling up to my
original take profit this is supposed to
get here in a day or two
um but yeah this has clearly got in here
a lot faster am I making a logical
business decision am I making a logical
trading decision am I getting out of the
trade because it's hit my take profit or
am I getting out of the trade because
it's hit a round number of 50 000 and I
want to make fifty thousand or twenty
five thousand seventy five we're
attached to these round numbers for
whatever reason it's such a
psychological barrier but let's say you
want to get out at 50 000 but it's so
further away from where you're original
take profit is you're tied to the money
at that point so that's going to leave
me to my third point is don't be greed
don't set and forget too much if I would
have held this trade for I think it was
another day and a half I could have made
easily 150 200 maybe even a quarter mil
because the train obviously kept going
but at that point it wasn't a logical
business decision holding the trade for
that long would have simply being greed
and all of these three needs to be tied
together because if one of them are out
of sync when you go take your next trade
you're not going to make a logical
decision you need to have the same
approach to every single trade let's say
I take the exact same setup on goal the
same exact setup I had in Gold but let's
say on GJ I'm not going to think to
myself oh if I would have held this
trade last time for an extra day and a
half I would have made an extra 100K
because if you come into that then at
that point you're just being greedy
you're not making a logical business
decision you have to keep it you know
with the rules and everything according
to your trading plan so with that being
said join the free telegram gems there
all the time hit the subscribe everybody
and it helps me out a lot it motivates
me you know keep pushing video out to
you guys drop a comment if this video
helped if it was you know dope gave some
dope insights if you guys like the
comment um the content and I'll see you
guys in the next video